the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from hundreds of them IT
进行捐赠或查看附加材料由数百人资讯
courses
课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT that EDU hard
麻省理工学院的EDU硬
the
该
the in
在该
the norm
规范
are
有
the in the last two lectures
对在过去的两个讲座
and we saw how periodic not periodic signals could be represented as linear
我们看到周期性不是周期性的信号是如何可以表示为线性
combinations a complex exponentials
组合的复指数
and this led to the Fourier series representation
这导致了傅里叶级数表示
in the periodic case and it led to the Fourier transform
在周期的情况下，这导致了傅里叶变换
representation in the a periodic case and and then in fact
在一个周期的情况下，并然后实际上表示
what we did was to incorporate the 4e a series
我们所做的是把该4E系列
within the framework of the Fourier transform what I'd like to do in today's
傅立叶的框架内变换了我想要做在今天的
lecture is
讲座
look at the 4-yard transform more closely
看4码更紧密地变换
in particular with regard to so this property's
尤其是关于所以这个属性的
so let me begin by reminding you
所以首先请允许我提醒你
love the analysis and synthesis equations for the four th
爱的分析和综合方程四个次
transform and as I summarize them here
变换和我在这里总结一下他们
the synthesis equation being a
合成公式是一个
an equation that tells us how to build the
一个方程，它告诉我们如何建立
time function outta in essence a linear combination
在本质上的时间功能失控的线性组合
a complex exponentials and the analysis equation
一个复指数和分析方程
telling us how to get the amplitudes love those complex exponentials
告诉我们如何得到振幅喜欢那些复杂的指数函数
from the Associated time function
从相关的时间函数
so essentially in the decomposition
所以基本上在分解
affect safety as a linear combination of complex exponentials
影响安全为复指数的线性组合
the complex amplitudes if those are in effect
如果复振幅的那些是有效
the 48 transform scaled by
48通过变换缩放
the differential and scaled by one over two-part
差分和由1以上两部分的比例
now as
现在为
I indicated last time the 48 transform
我表示最后一次变换48
is a complex function of frequency in
是频率的复变函数中
and in particular the complex function of frequency
以及在特定的频率的复函数
has an important and very useful cemetery property
有一个重要的和非常有用的墓地财产
the symmetry love the Fourier transform
对称性爱傅立叶变换
when X if T is real is
当X如果T是真实的就是
what is referred to as conjugate symmetric in other words if we take the
什么被称为换句话说共轭对称的，如果我们取
complex
复杂
function after Omega and and its complex conjugate
功能后，欧米茄和其共轭复数
that's equivalent to replacing Omega
这相当于更换欧米茄
by minus Omega and a consequence if that
通过减去欧米茄和后果，如果该
if we think interns love the real party the Fourier transform
如果我们认为实习生热爱真正的党的傅里叶变换
the real part is and even function of frequency
实部和频率的偶函数
and the magnet to is an even function of frequency
和磁铁对是频率的偶函数
whereas the imaginary part is an
而虚数部分是一个
odd function of frequency and the phase angle
频率的奇函数和相位角
is an odd function of frequency so
是频率的奇函数，以便
we have this symmetry relationship that for except the real
我们有这种对称关系，对于除了真正的
if we think I've either the real part or the magnitude of the Fourier transform
如果我们想我已经不是真正的部分或傅立叶变换幅度
its even symmetric and the imaginary part
其甚至对称和虚部
or the phase angle either one it is
或相位角的任一个是
fought symmetric in other words if we flip it we multiply by a minus sign
换句话说，打对称，如果我们将其翻转，我们乘上一个减号
let's didn't look at an example
让我们没有看一个例子
in the context love an example that we worked last time
在上下文的爱，我们的工作最后一次的例子
for the Fourier transform we took
对于傅里叶变换，我们把
the case both a real exponential
在这两种情况下，一个真正的指数
love the form eat to the -80 times this step
爱的形式能吃到-80倍这一步
and the 48 transform as
和48变换为
we found was other algebraic form one over a plus J Omega
我们发现了一个加Ĵ欧米茄等代数中一
and incidently the 48 transform into grow only converged
顺便说一句，并在48变身为仅增长收敛
for a greater than 0 in other words
为0，换句话说大于
for this exponential became and I illustrated
该指数成为和我说明
the magnitude and angle and what we see is that
幅度和角度，我们看到的是，
you the minus 8c is a real
你负8C是一个真正的
time function therefore its magnitude
因此，时间函数的幅度
should be an even function of frequency and indeed it is
应频率的偶函数，实际上它是
and its phase angle shown below
和下图所示的相位角
is and odd function of frequency
是和频率的奇函数
so in fact in although
所以实际上，虽然中
I stressed last time that
我强调最后一次
the complex exponentials required to build the time function
建立时间功能所需的复指数
require exponentials both positive and negative frequencies
要求指数函数的正面和负面的频率
for except the real what we see is that
的，除了真正的，我们看到的是，
because if the symmetry properties either for the real and imaginary or
因为如果对称特性无论是对实部和虚或
magnitude and angle
幅值和相角
we can specify a before you transform for let's say only positive frequencies
我们可以指定一个你变换让我们说只有正频率前
and asymmetry then implies are tells us
和不对称然后暗示顷告诉我们
what the Fourier transform then will be for the negative frequencies
傅立叶变换那么什么将是负的频率
okay now this same example the cause
现在没事了同样的例子的原因
the decaying exponential demonstrates
该指数衰减演示
another important and often useful
另一个重要的和经常有用
property the Fourier transform
属性的傅立叶变换
specifically let's rewrite algebraically this example
特别让我们重写代数这个例子
as I indicate here so we have
我在此说明，所以我们有
again the exponential was 48 transformers one over a plus J Omega
再次指数为48变压器一个比一个加Ĵ欧米茄
and if I A just simply divide numerator and denominator by a
如果IA只是一个简单的划分分子和分母
I can rewrite it in the form shown here
我可以在这里显示的形式改写
and what we notice is dead in the time function
我们注意到什么是死在时间功能
we have a term of the form eight times TV
我们有形式八次电视的任期
and in the frequency function we have a term for the form Omega
而在频功能我们为形式欧米茄期
divided by a or
由一个或分
equivalent Lee we can't think all the
李相等于我们不能认为所有的
time function which I show here
时间函数，我在这里展示
and as the pram enter a gets smaller
和婴儿车进入变小
the exponential gets spread out in time
该指数被摊开在时间
whereas s04e08 transform
而s04e08变换
or the magnitude of its Fourier transform has the inverse property
或它的傅立叶变换的幅度变换具有逆属性
that as a get smaller in fact
，作为一个获得事实上小
this scales down in frequency
这个比例降低频率
well this is a general property love
嗯，这是一个一般财产的爱情
the Fourier transform namely the fact
傅立叶变换即事实
that a a linear scaling a time
一个线性缩放时间
generates the infers linear scaling a frequency
生成所推导线性缩放的频率
and the general statement love this time frequency scaling is what
和一般的语句爱这一次的频率缩放是什么
I show at the top above the transparency namely the equation
我展示上面的透明性，即方程顶部
that if we scale the time function in time
如果我们在缩放时的时间函数
then we apply and infers scaling a frequency
那么我们申请并推断缩放频率
now her this in fact is probably a result
现在她的这个其实是很可能的结果
that you're already possibly familiar with in
那你可能已经熟悉了
somewhat of a different context essentially you can think of this
有所不同的上下文中基本上你能想到的这
as an example poor generalization rather
作为一个例子不佳而泛化
up the notion that if let's say I A
起来的概念，如果让我们说我一个
had a signal that was recorded on a tape player
有被记录在磁带上的播放器，信号
and if I play the tape back and let's say twice the speed which means that I'm
如果我打带回来，让我们说，速度的两倍，这意味着我
compressing the time axis
压缩时间轴
linearly by a factor of two then in fact what happens is that
线性是由两个因素那么实际上是发生了什么了
the frequencies that we observe get pushed up by a factor of two
我们观察到的频率将被推由两个因素
and effect let me illustrate that
和效果让我说明，
I have here a glockenspiel
我这里有一个钟琴
and anyone who loves a parade certainly knows what I each
和任何人谁喜欢游行肯定知道我每
blockage feel as and
堵塞觉得和
this particular glockenspiel has
这个特殊的钟琴有
3 eighties separated each by an active there's a middle way
3八十年代分隔每个由一个活跃的还有一条中间道路
a high a us and a low a
高一我们和低一
and what I've done is to record
而我所做的就是记录
the middle a on a tape
在磁带上的中间
at seven and a half inches per second and
以每秒七个半英寸
what I'd like to demonstrate is that as
我想证明的是，作为
we play that back either a cloister half-speed
我们玩了回一个回廊半速
the effective note gets moved down or up by a doctor
有效的音符越向下移动，或由医生
so let me first play the note at
所以让我先玩的音符
the speed at which was recorded and so what we'll hear
的速度记录，所以我们会听到
is the middle a as i've recorded it and let me just start
是中间的一个，因为我已经记录了它，让我刚开始
the tape player
所述带播放器
okay let me stop it and hopefully what you heard is the
好吧，让我停下来，希望你听到的是什么
same note from the tape recorder as
同一帖由录音机作为
the note that I played on the glockenspiel okay well now
我演奏的钟琴还好现在好了的音符
a rewind the tape and we go back to the beginning
一个将磁带倒，我们回到开头
love that portion and
爱那部分和
now if I change the tapes the to
现在如果我更改了磁带到
half the speed so from seven and a half inches per second
一半的速度，因此从每秒7英寸半
a change the tape speed 233 quarter
一个改变磁带速度233季
inches per second and now
每秒现在英寸
when I play the tape back because effect because
当我播放磁带回来，因为效果，因为
love the inverse relationship between time and frequency scaling we're now
爱的时间和频率缩放之间的反比关系，我们现在是
scaling in time by stretching out we would expect the frequencies to be
在缩放时间伸展出我们所期望的频率是
lowered
降低
by a factor of two we should now expect the
由两个因素，我们现在应该期待
taped no to be an octave lower
录音没有成为一个低八度
matching the slower a so let's just play that okay let me stop it
匹配慢所以让我们只玩那好吧，让我停下来
and again will rewind the tape
并再次将快倒磁带
go back to
回去
the beginning and now will play this at
一开始，现在将在玩这个
twice the speed so I change from three and three-quarters
速度的两倍，所以我从三个四分之三改变
to 15 inches per second and now and I play it we would expect that
到15英寸每秒，现在和我玩它，我们可以预料，
to match the upper no and let's just do that Ste
匹配上没有，让我们只是做了科技教育
us
us okay well
我们也没关系
although thats a result that intuitively probably
虽然那是一个结果直观地可能
makes considerable sense in fact what that is
使得相当意义的事实是什么
is an illustration love the inverse relationship between
是一个例证爱之间的反比关系
time scaling frequency scaling and also by the way it was finally my opportunity
时间频率缩放比例，也顺便说一下这是我的最后机会
to play the glockenspiel on television okayed now
打钟琴在电视上现在okayed
in in addition their is another
在另外他们是另一种
very important relationship between the time and frequency domains
时域和频域之间的很重要的关系
namely what is referred to as a
即什么被称为
duality relationship and
对偶关系，
the duality relationship between time and frequency
时间与频率之间的对偶关系
falls out more less directly from
掉下来更多少直接从
the equations the analysis and synthesis equations in particular if we look at
方程特别是分析和综合方程，如果我们看一下
the
该
synthesis equation which I repeat here
我在这里重复合成公式
and the analysis equation which I repeat below it
并且我重复它下面的分析方程
what we observe is dead in fact
我们观察到什么是死在事实上
these equations are basically identical
这些方程是基本一致
except for the fact that in the top
除了一个事实，即在顶部
integral we have things as a function of Omega in the bottom integral as a
整体我们有事情，欧米茄的函数在底部积分作为
function of T
的T功能
and there's a factor of 10 ver tu Pai and by the way a minus sign
并有10个版本杜白和方式减号的因素
well you can look at the algebra
还有你可以看看代数
more carefully at your leisure but especially with this says
更仔细地在您的休闲，但特别是与此说
is that if excessive Omega is
是，如果过多的欧米茄
the Fourier transform over type function exit see
傅里叶变换在类型的函数退出见
then in fact except Amy
那么实际上，除了艾米
is very much like the Fourier transform affective Omega
是很像的傅里叶变换情感欧米茄
in fact it's the Fourier transform attacks have minus Omega
其实它的傅里叶变换攻击有减欧米茄
to account for this minus sign and by the way there's just an additional
考虑到这一点减号和方式还有的只是一个额外的
factor
因素
one over 25 so the duality relationship which
一个比25这样的对偶关系，
follows from these two equations in fact
遵循从事实上这两个方程
says that if x50
说，如果X50
an ex vivo maker are a4e a transformed pair
离体壶A4E转化成对
if little accent capital XR Fourier transform pair
如果一点口音资本XR傅立叶变换对
then capital lacks in fact has a $4 EA transform
当时的资本缺乏，其实有4美元的EA变换
which is proportional a little lax turned around well
这是成正比稍有不慎转身以及
this to outdo ality in the continuous time Fourier transform
这胜过先进而精湛的连续时间傅立叶变换
is very important it's very useful it by the way is not
是很重要的它是非常有用的它的方式是不
duality that surface in a forty a series because as you recall the 48 series
二元性的表面在40系列，因为当你回想起48系列
begins with a continuous-time function
开始于一个连续时间函数
and in the frequency domain generates a sequence
并且在频域中产生序列
which with just naturally have the proper have
这与只是自然有正确的有
problems associated with it if we attempted to
与之相关联，如果我们试图问题
interpreted to ality and we'll see also:
解释为先进而精湛的，我们也将看到：
that in a discrete-time case one of the important differences between
在离散时间情况之间的重要区别之一
continuous-time and discrete-time Fourier transforms
连续时间和离散时间傅里叶变换
is the fact that in continuous-time we have to our the
的事实是，在连续时间，我们不得不把该
in discrete-time for then the discrete-time Fourier transform we don't
在离散时间则离散时间傅里叶变换，我们不
well
好
let's indicate illustrate this with an example
让我们表示用一个例子来说明这一点
in here are in fact two examples
在这里，其实是两个例子
a Fourier transform pairs taken from examples in the text
傅立叶变换的例子，在文中对拍摄
to the top one being example
顶端的一个是例子
four-point 11 from the tax and it's a time for action
四点11从税收，这是一个行动的时候了
which is a sin 0 X over X type a function
这是一种罪过0 X在X型的函数
and its Fourier transform
及其傅立叶变换
corresponds to a
对应于一个
rectangular shape in the frequency domain there's also
矩形形状在频域中有也
another example in the text the example the preseason this one
在文本的例子中，这个季前赛另一个例子
which is example four-point 10 and an example four point 10
这是例子四点10和示例四点10
we begin with a rectangle
我们以一个矩形
and its Fourier transform is love the form
及其傅立叶变换是爱的形式
all a sin x over X function
所有的罪过倍过X功能
so in fact if we look at these to
所以其实如果我们看看这些以
examples together what we see is
一起的例子我们看到的是
the duality very evident in other words
二元性非常明显，换句话说
if we take this time function and
如果我们把这个时间的功能和
instead think i've a frequency function that has the same form
而不是想我有一个频率函数具有相同的形式
then we simply interchange the rolls a time-frequency
那么我们简单地交换辊时频
in the other domains so the fact that these to correspond
在其他领域这样一个事实，即这些对应
means that these two cars find
也就是说，这两款车找
course and in this particular example
当然，在这特殊的例子
we because it the fact that we picked a symmetric function even function
我们因为我们选择了一个对称函数偶函数的事实
in fact the additional twist love the time axis being reversed didn't show up
其实更多的爱扭轴被逆转的时间未露面
in her in duality with this example
在她的对偶这个例子
now one thing he says of course is that essentially
现在有一件事，他说当​​然是本质
anytime you've calculated
任何时候你已经计算
the 48 transform a one-time function
48变换一次性功能
then you actually calculate the Fourier transform
那么你实际计算傅立叶变换
to type functions another one being
键入函数另一个是
the dual example to the one that you just calculated
双例子，你刚刚计算出的值
now also somewhat related to do our the
现在也有些做我们的相关
is what is referred to as parce balls
是什么被称为parce球
relation for the continuous-time Fourier transform
关系的连续时间傅立叶变换
and essentially what parts are false relationship says
而且基本上什么部位都是假的关系说
is that as kind of a a summary other
是那种作为一个其他汇总
it says dead the energy
它说死了的能量
in a time function and the energy
在一个时间函数和能量
in its Fourier transform are proportional the proportionality factor
在它的傅里叶变换是成正比的比例系数
being a factor of two pi
作为两个圆周率的一个因素
it well that summarized here what's meant by the energy
它清楚，在这里总结什么是由能量
is course the ago the magnitude squared effect City
当然是以前的幅度平方影响市
and the statement apart the balls relation and is dead
并且该语句分开球关系，是死的
that in a brawl the energy and accept T
在争吵的能量，并接受Ŧ
is proportional to this integral which is the energy
正比于这个积分这是能量
indexable Megan now
现在梅根可转位
although we've incorporated the 4e a series
虽然我们已经成立了4E系列
within a framework for the Fourier transform parcels relation
为傅立叶框架内变换包裹关系
needs to be modified slightly for
需要略微修改为
for a series because the fact that periodic signal
对于一个系列，因为事实周期信号
has an infinite amount of energy and its and essentially
具有能量和无限量的，基本上
that former parcels relationship for the periodic case would say
对于周期性的情况下，前幅的关系会说
infinity equals infinity which isn't too useful
无穷大等于无穷大，这是不是太有用
however can be modified so that part's a false relationship for the periodic case
但是可以进行修改，以使一部分的用于周期性情况下的假关系
says essentially that the energy E
本质上说，该能量E
in one period other periodic time function
在一个周期内其他周期性时间函数
in is proportional with this is the proportionality factor
在是成比例的，这是比例系数
proportional to the sum %uh the magnitude squared
成比例的总和％呃的幅度平方
up the coefficients in other words the energy in one period
向上换句话说能量在一个周期中的系数
is proportional to the energy in the sequence
正比于能量序列中的
that represents the four EA series coefficients
表示4 EA系列系数
now okay there are lots of other properties
还好现在有很多其他属性
and there developed in the text in the study guide
而且在学习指导文本研制
a number a properties that we want to make particular you so
一个数字，我们要特别的你这么一个属性
during this lecture and in later lectures
在本次讲座，并在以后的讲座
are ones that I summarize here and
都是我在这里总结和
I won't demonstrate the proves but
我不会表现出了证明，但
a principally focus on some with the interpretation is the lecture goes on
一，主要集中在一些与解释是讲座的推移
well in the first property that I have listed here's what's referred to as the
以及在我这里列出的第一个属性是什么的简称
time shifting property
时移特性
and the time shifting property says if I have a time function
和时移物业说，如果我有时间的函数
with a Fourier transform mexico maker
用傅里叶变换墨西哥制造商
if I shift that time function in time
如果我在时间的转变，时间功能
dan that corresponds to multiplying
担对应相乘
the 48 transformed by this factor
受这一因素改变了48
now as you examine this factor what you can see is that
现在，当你审视这个因素你可以看到的是，
this factor has magnitude unity
这个因素有震级团结
and it has a phase which is linear with frequency
并且它有一个相，其是线性的频率
and is slow %uh minus 20
和缓慢％呃零下20
so a statement to remember that will come up
这样的声明是要记住，上来了
many times throughout the cores
很多时候整个内核
is that a timeshare after a displacement in time
是在时间上的位移后分时度假
corresponds to linear phase
对应于线性相位
or change in linear phase earlier change in phase and frequency
或线性相位改变相位和频率变化的前面
another property in and in fact a pair of properties
在和实际上是对属性的另一个属性
that will make reference to as we turn our attention toward the end of this
这将使参考，因为我们把我们的注意力转向本月底
lecture to
讲课
solving differential equations using the Fourier transform
采用傅里叶变换求解微分方程
is hit was referred to as the differentiation property
被击中被称为分化特性
and its companion which is the integration property
和它的同伴也就是集成特性
the differentiation property says again if we have
分化属性再次说，如果我们有
a time function whose with Fourier transform mexico maker
一个时间函数，其与傅里叶变换墨西哥制造商
the Fourier transform up the time derivative that
傅里叶变换了的时间导数是
is in corresponds to multiplying the Fourier transform
是在对应于乘以傅立叶变换
by a linear function of frequency so
通过频率的线性函数，所以
here it's a linear able to change dead
在这里它是一个线性能改变死
that corresponds to differentiation
对应于分化
now at first glance what you might think is that
现在乍一看你可能会认为那是什么
the integration property is just the reverse if that if
整合财产则刚刚相反，如果，如​​果
for the differentiation property you multiply by J Omega then
为分化属性，你为J欧米茄然后乘以
for integration you must abide by jail maker and thats almost correct
整合必须由监狱制造商遵守和那几乎是正确的
except not quite and the reason for the not quite
除了不太并为不太理由
is that recall that if you differentiate
是召回，如果您区分
what happens of course is that you lose a constant
会发生什么，当然是你失去一个常数
and if we have a time function thats some fun and energy signal plus a
如果我们有一个时间函数那一些乐趣和能量信号加一个
constant
不变
differentiating will destroy the constant
差分会破坏不变
and integration the immigration property in essence tries to bring that back
并集成在本质上是移民财产试图把那句话
so the integration property which is the inverse
这样的整合属性也就是逆
of the differentiation property says that we divide
分化物业说，我们把
the transformed by J Omega and then
转化为J欧米茄，然后
if in fact their was a constant added to accept T
如果事实上他们是一个常数加入到接受Ŧ
we have to account for that by inserting an impulse
我们必须通过插入一个冲动，占该
into the Fourier transform and
成付里叶变换，并
the file property that I want to draw your attention to
我想提请你注意这个文件属性
on this you graph is the linearity property
关于这一点，你的图形是线性特性
which is very straight forward to demonstrate from
这是非常简单的从展示
the analysis and synthesis equations which simply said is
分析和综合方程，简单地说就是
if X 100 maker is the Fourier transform X 1ft
如果X 100制造者是傅立叶X变换1英尺
and x2 Omega is the Fourier transform X 2ft
和x2欧米茄是傅立叶X变换2英尺
then the Fourier transform a linear combination is
然后傅里叶变换的线性组合被
a linear combination love the Fourier transforms
线性组合爱的傅里叶变换
now let me emphasize also that these properties for the most part
现在让我也强调，这些属性在大多数情况下
apply both 240 a series and Fourier transforms
同时适用于240系列和傅立叶变换
because in fact and what we've done is to incorporate
因为实际上和我们所做的是把
the forty a series within the
第四十一个系列中的
framework of the Fourier transform
的傅立叶变换的框架
okay now will be using a number of these properties shortly when we turn our
还好现在可以使用一些这些属性不久，当我们把我们的
attention to
注意
near-constant coefficient differential equations however before we do that I'd
近常系数微分方程但是之前我们做的，我会
like to
喜欢
focus on two additional
专注于两个附加
major properties and
主要性能和
these are what are referred to as the convolution property and the modulation
这些是被称为卷积特性和调制
property
属性
and in fact the convolution property as I'm about
而事实上卷积财产作为我对
to introduces forms the
以介绍形式
mathematical and conceptual basis for
数学和概念基础
the whole notion of filtering which in fact will be
滤波的整个概念这实际上将是
a topic by itself in a set of lectures and
本身在一组讲座主题，
and in fact is a chapter by itself in the textbook
而实际上是由它本身的教科书一个章节
similarly what i'll refer to as the modulation property
同样我会称之为调制特性
again well occupy its own set
再次也占据了自己的一套
have lectures as we go through this scores and in fact has its own
有讲座，我们通过这个分数，事实上都有自己的
a chapter in the textbook
在教科书的章节
let me in just indicate what the convolution property is
让我在短短的表示卷积属性是什么
and and what the convolution property
和什么卷积财产
tells us is that
告诉我们的是，
the 48 transform of the convolution
48变换的卷积
a two-time functions is the product
两年时间的函数是产品
all therefore yea transforms
因此，所有的转换啊
so it says for example dead
所以说，例如死
if I have a linear time-invariant system
如果我有一个线性时不变系统
and in I have an input exits the an impulse response HFT
而在我有一个输入退出的脉冲响应HFT
and the output of course being the convolution
和过程的输出即卷积
then in fact if I look at this in the frequency domain
那么实际上，如果我看这在频域
the Fourier transform up the output
傅里叶变换了输出
is the for EA transform the input
是对EA变换输入
times the Fourier transform the impulse response
倍的傅里叶变换的脉冲响应
now you can demonstrate this property
现在你能证明这个属性
algebraically by essentially taking the convolution integral
通过代数基本上采取的卷积积分
and applying to 48 transforming doing the appropriate
并应用到48变换做适当的
in a changing the order integration et cetera
在不断变化的顺序整合等等
but who what I'd like to draw your attention to is a
但谁是我想提请你注意的是一
somewhat more intuitive interpretation of the property
该物业较为直观的解释
and the intuitive interpretations stems from
和直观的诠释源于
the relationship between the Fourier transform at the impulse response
变换的脉冲响应的傅立叶之间的关系
and what we refer to as the frequency response
和我们所说的频率响应
now recall dead wanna have
现在回忆想死了
the things that lettuce to use complex exponentials as building blocks
莴苣使用复指数作为积木的事
was the fact that there I can functions linear time-invariant systems in other
是事实，有我可以函数的线性时不变系统的其他
words
话
if we have linear time-invariant system
如果我们有线性时不变系统
and I have an input which is a complex exponential
我有一个输入，是一个复杂的指数
the output is a complex exponential the same frequency
输出是一个复杂的指数相同的频率
multiplied by what we call the frequency response
乘以就是我们所说的频率响应
and in fact the expression for the frequency response
而且事实上对频率响应中的表达
is identical to the expression for the four EA transform the impulse response
是相同的四个EA的表达变换的脉冲响应
in other words the frequency response is
换句话说，频率响应是
the Fourier transform of the impulse response
的脉冲响应的傅立叶变换
now in that context how can we
现在，在这方面我们怎么能
interpret the convolution property well
解读卷积性质以及
remember what I said at the beginning the lecture 1 I've pointed
记得我在开始时所说的讲座1我已经指出
to the synthesis equation and I said in
到合成方程和I中所述
in essence the synthesis equation tells us
在本质上是合成公式告诉我们
how to decompose x50 as a linear combination a complex exponentials
如何分解X50作为线性组合一个复指数
what are the complex amplitudes are those complex exponentials
什么是复振幅是那些复杂的指数函数
well interns love our notation year
以及实习生热爱我们的符号一年
the complex amplitude of those complex exponentials
这些复杂的指数函数的复振幅
is Xserve Omega or proportional taxable make in particular taxable make a deal
是的Xserve欧米茄或特定比例应课税化妆课税作出处理
maker
制造者
and then a factor two-part well
然后一个因数两部分组成的井
as this signal goes through this linear time-invariant system
因为这个信号通过这种线性时不变系统
what happens to each of those exponentials is
发生了什么每个这些指数函数是
it each one gets multiplied by the frequency response
它的每一个被乘以频率响应
at The Associated frequency
在相关的频率
what comes out is the amplitude
随之而来的是幅度
all the complex exponentials that are used
所有所使用的复指数
to bill the output
到帐单输出
so in fact the convolution property
所以实际上卷积财产
simply is telling us
只需告诉我们
that interns have a decomposition the signal
实习生有一个分解的信号
enters a complex exponentials as we push that signal through linear
进入复指数作为我们推动该信号通过线性
time-invariant system
时不变系统
were separately modifying with the frequency response were multiplying
分别与频率响应分别乘以修改
by the frequency response the amplitudes
由频率响应的幅值
love the exponential comp phones used to build the input
爱用来建立输入指数排版手机
and that song intern is
而这首歌是实习生
the decomposition of the output in terms of complex exponentials
的输出中的复指数方面的分解
now and I I understand that kinda going through that involves
现在和II明白，有点经历，涉及
a little bit of sorting out and I strongly encourage you
整理出的一点点，我强烈建议您
to try to understand and interpret the convolution property
试着去了解和解释的卷积性质
in knows conceptual terms rather than simply by
在知道概念上，而不是简单地通过
applying the mathematics to the convolution integral and seeing that
应用数学卷积积分，看到那
terms match up on both sides
条件匹配的两侧
now as i indicated the convolution property
现在，正如我卷积财产
forms the basis for what's referred to as filtering
构成的基础发生了什么被称为滤波
and this is a topic that will be treating a
这是将要治疗的课题
considerable amount of detail and after
细节和相当数量后，
we've also gone through a discussion love the discrete-time Fourier transform
我们通过讨论也没有了爱的离散时间傅立叶变换
in the next several lectures however what I'd like to do is just
在接下来的几次讲座但是我想要做的就是
just indicate now a little bit love
只是表示现在一点点的爱
the conceptual ideas involve
概念性的想法涉及
essentially conceptually what filtering as its
本质概念是什么过滤作为其
typically referred to corresponds to
通常被称为对应于
is modifying separately
单独修改
the individual frequency components in a signal
在一个信号中的各个频率分量
the convolution property told us that if we
卷积属性告诉我们，如果我们
look at the individual frequency comp points they get multiplied by the
看看各个频率comp点，他们的得到乘以
frequency response and so what that says is that we can amplify or it anyway
频率响应，还等什么，说的是，我们可以放大或也无妨
any of those comp own it separately using a linear time-invariant system
分别采用线性时不变系统任何该等排版拥有它
for example what I've illustrated here is
比如我在这里说明的是
the frequency response what is commonly referred to
的频率响应通常所说到
as and ideal Lopez filter what an ideal 0 pass filter does
作为与理想洛佩兹过滤器什么是理想的0通滤波器做
is to pass exactly
为准确传递
frequencies in one frequency range
在一个频率范围内的频率
and eliminate totally frequencies outside that range
并消除该范围之外的频率完全
another filter which is not so ideal might for example
另一种过滤器，它也不是那么理想可以例如
attenuate sit com phone it's in this band but not
衰减静坐COM的电话是在这个频段，但不
I rather attenuate conference in this band but not totally eliminate them
我宁愿衰减发布会在这个频段，但不能完全消除它们
now interns a filtering we can think back
现在实习生的过滤，我们可以回想
to the differentiation property and in fact interpreter
向分化特性及其实解释器
differentiation or differentiator as a filter
差异化或差异化作为一个过滤器
recall that the differentiation property said
记得分化物业说
that the Fourier transform all the differentiated signal
该傅里叶变换的所有的差分信号
is the for a transformer the original signal multiplied by J Omega
是用于变压器的原信号相乘者J欧米茄
so what that says then
还等什么，说再
is dead if we have a differentiator opened the frequency response to that
是死的，如果我们有一个区别开了频率响应的
is J Omega in other words the Fourier transform of the output is Jay Omega
为j欧米茄换句话说傅立叶输出的变换是周杰伦欧米茄
times the Fourier transform the input
时间傅立叶变换的输入
and so the frequency response a differentiator
和这样的频率响应一个微分
looks like this and turns its magnitude and what it does
貌似这个和原来的大小和它做什么
of course is it amplifies high frequencies
当然是它放大高频
and attenuates low frequencies
并衰减低频
well let me just to kinda cement summer these ideas
还有让我来还挺水泥夏天这些想法
illustrate them in a context 0
说明它们在上下文中0
one kind of signal namely signal which in fact
一种信号，即信号实际上
is the spatial signal rather than a time signal
是空间的信号，而不是一个时间信号
and this also gives me an opportunity to introduce you
这也让我有机会向你们介绍
to our colleague JBJ for EA's
我们的同事JBJ为EA的
so if we could look at our colleague mister four EA
因此，如果我们可以看看我们的同事老总4 EA
who by the way is on
谁的方式是
not only person who had tremendously brilliant insights
不仅是谁了巨大的辉煌人的见解
and his insights in fact have led to
他其实见解导致
the developments really for the foundation the developments that
的发展确实为基础的事态发展
is the basis for this course he was also a very interesting fascinating person
是基础这门课程，他也是一个非常有趣的引人入胜人
and there's a certain amount of historical discussion
并有一定的历史讨论
about for EA and his background which you might enjoy reading in the text
有关EA和他的背景，你可能会喜欢阅读的文本
in any case what you're looking at a course is a signal
在任何情况下，你正在寻找一个疗程是什么信号
and the signal is a spatial signal and
和信号是空间信号和
it has high frequencies and low frequencies high frequencies
它具有高频率和低频率的高频率
corresponding to things that are varying rapidly
对应于正在迅速变化的事
spatially and low frequencies barings
空间和低频霸菱
very slowly spatially it so
非常缓慢地在空间上是这样
for example we could low-pass filter
例如，我们可以低通滤波器
this picture simply by asking
这幅画只问
the video crew if they could slightly defocus
视频船员，如果他们能稍微散焦
and what you see as the picture is the focus if you can hold it there
和你看到的图片是什么焦点，如果你能保持不动，
is dead we've lost edges which
死了，我们已经失去了它的边缘
is the rapid variation and what we've retained is the broader
是快速变化和我们所保留的是更广泛的
slow variation and now let's take out
缓慢的变化，现在让我们拿出
the d focusing low-pass filter and go back
对d聚焦的低通滤波器，然后返回
to a focused image
到聚焦图像
okay now what
现在没事了什么
and we can also consider is what would happen if we look
而且我们还可以考虑的是，如果我们看一下会发生什么
at the differentiated image and their are several ways that we can think about
在差异化的形象和他们的几种方法，大家可以想想
this
这
one is that a differentiator of course the output of a differentiator
一种是理所当然的微分器微分器的输出端
is larger where the discontinuity
是其中较大的不连续性
or where the variation is faster
或其中的变化是快
and so we would expect the edges
所以我们希望的边缘
to be enhanced if in fact we differentiated the image
如果事实上我们差异化的形象得到提升
or if we interpret differentiation in the context
或者如果我们的解释分化的背景下，
love our filter then what we're saying
爱我们的过滤器，然后我们在说什么
if hey what we're saying is that in effect
如果哎就是我们要说的是，在效果
what's happening is that the differentiator is
所发生的事情是，区别在于
accentuating the high frequencies
加剧的高频率
because if the frequency shape the differentiator now recall that this all
因为如果频率塑造与众不同现在回忆起来，这一切
kinda fits together is a nice package
还挺适合在一起是一个不错的包
be expected to actively the differentiation will enhance ages
可以预期，积极的分化将加强青睐
when we talked about square waves and we so I have a for a series built up a
当我们谈到方波，然后我们让我有一种为一系列建立了
square wave
方波
we saw that it was the high frequencies
我们看到，这是高频率
that were required in order to build up the sharp
须以建立锋利的
edges and so either viewed as a filter or viewed intuitively
边缘，因此无论是看作是一个滤波器或直观地观察
we would expect that the differentiated image would in fact
我们期望有区别的图像会在事实上
get would in fact it anyway the slowly varying background and amplify
得到实际上会也无妨的缓慢变化的背景和放大
the rapidly varying ages so let's look again at
在迅速变化的年龄让我们再来看看
our original image just to remind you love the fact that there are edges of
我们原来的形象只是为了提醒你爱的事实，也有边缘
course and their
当然和他们的
is more slowly varying backgrounds
更是缓慢变化的背景
and now let's look at the
现在就让我们来看看
result love passing that through
结果爱传递，通过
a differentiator and as i think is
微分和我认为是
very evident in that in the resulting image
在于，在所述生成的图像非常明显
clearly is the edges that a retained and
清楚的是，一个保留和边缘
the slow back to slower background variations
慢回较慢的背景变化
are destroyed which is consistent with everything we've said
被摧毁这与一切，我们已经一致表示，
okay now i've emphasized the her will be returning
还好现在我已经强调了她将回到
to a much broader discussion a filtering at
到更广泛的讨论在过滤
a later point in the cores right now like to comment on another
在内核后面的点，现在喜欢上另一个评论
property which here is also as i indicated a topic I've
财产，在这里也正如我的话题我已经
in its own right and which really is the dual
在自己的权利，哪些是真正的双
property to the convolution property and in fact could be argued directly from
属性为卷积财产，事实上可以直接从被争论
duality
二元性
and that is what's referred to as the modulation property
这就是发生了什么被称为调制特性
now the convolution property told us that
现在卷积属性告诉我们，
if we convolved in the time domain we multiply in the frequency domain
如果我们卷积在时域中乘以我们在频域
and we know the time and frequency domains are interchangeable because it
而且我们知道时间域和频率域是可以互换的，因为它
to our the
我们的
so what that would suggest is dead
还等什么，从而说明是死的
if we multiply in the time domain
如果我们乘以在时域
that would correspond to convolution in the frequency domain
这将对应于卷积在频域
and in fact head that is exactly what the modulation property is
而事实上头是这样的调制特性是什么
I have a summarized here that if we multiply
我有一个在这里总结，如果我们乘
a time function by another time function then
另一个时间函数时间函数，那么
in the frequency domain week involved
在所涉及的频域周
whereas the convolution property is just the duel at that
而卷积属性只是决斗在那
namely convolved being in the time domain corresponds to
即卷积在时域中是对应于
multiplication in the frequency domain
乘法在频域
the convolution property is the basis as i indicated for filtering
卷积属性为基础正如我进行过滤
the modulation property as I've summarized it here
因为我在这里总结它的调制特性
in fact is the entire basis
实际上是整个基础
for amplitude modulation systems issues
振幅调制系统的问题
almost universally in communications and wait
几乎普遍在通信和等待
the modulation property is we'll see when we explored in more detail
调制特性是我们可以看到，当我们详细探讨
tells us is that if we have a signal with a certain spectrum
告诉我们的是，如果我们有一个信号具有一定的频谱
and we multiply by a sinusoidal
我们乘由正弦
signal whose for EA transformers said impulses
信号，其对EA变压器说冲动
then in a frequency-domain week involved and that corresponds
然后在所涉及的频域星期和对应
to taking the original spectrum and translating it
采取原始光谱并将其转换
shifting it in frequency up to
它移入频率高达
the frequency love the carrier namely
频爱的载体，即
the sinusoidal signal and as I said will
正弦信号，正如我说的意志
come to that in much more detail in a number of lectures
来的是，在一些讲座更加详细地
okay now we've seen a number of properties
好吧，现在我们已经看到了一些属性
and I indicated sometime earlier when we talked about
我表示前面的某个时候，当我们谈到
and differential equations that in fact it's the properties are the 48 transform
而且在事实上，它的属性是48变换微分方程
that providers with a very useful
这具有非常有用的提供
an important mechanism for solving linear constant coefficient differential
求解线性常系数微分方程的一个重要机制
equations
方程
and but I'd like to do now
和但我想现在要做的
is illustrate the procedure the basis for that
是说明该过程的基础，该
and I think what we'll do is illustrated simply in the context of several
我认为我们要做的仅仅是说明了几个上下文
examples
例子
okay well in what i've indicated is
还好还有在我所指示的
a system
系统
with her a an impulse response HFT
与她的脉冲响应HFT
or frequency response teachable nigga and of course we know that in the time
或频率响应受教黑人，当然，我们知道，在时间
domain it's just right to convolution
域它恰到好处地卷积
in the frequency domain its described through multiplication
在频域中的乘法，通过描述
and I in essence
和我在本质上
am assuming that we're talking about a linear time-invariant system
我假设我们谈论的是一个线性时不变系统
and we're also going to assume that it's characterized by a win here comes the
而且我们还假定，它的特点是一个双赢这里来的
coefficient differential equation
系数微分方程
where we're going to oppose the condition
我们要去的地方，反对的条件
that its causal linear and time-invariant
其因果线性时不变
or equivalent Lee that the initial condition conditions
或同等李初始条件条件
are consistent with initial rest
与最初的其余部分一致
and it's because it the fact that we're assuming
它是因为它是我们假定的事实
that is a linear time-invariant system that
这是一种线性时不变系统，它
we can describe it in the frequency domain through the convolution property
我们可以通过卷积属性描述了在频域
and we can use the properties love the forty a transfer
我们可以使用属性爱40转让
so let's take as our example a first-order differential equation
所以，让我们为我们的例子中一阶微分方程
as I indicate here so the derivative the output plus eight times the output is
我在这里表示，因此衍生的输出加上8倍的输出是
equal to the input
等于输入
and now we can use the differentiation property
现在我们可以使用差异化属性
if we for EA transform mystic entire expression
如果我们对EA变换神秘的整个表达式
the differentiation property tells us that
分化属性告诉我们，
the forty a transformer the derivative of the output
在40的变压器的输出的衍生
is the for a transformer the output multiplied by J Omega
是用于变压器的输出乘以者J欧米茄
and Lenny arity well let us
和Lenny元数以及让我们
right the Fourier transform love this as eight times while Omega
右边的傅立叶变换爱这个八倍，而欧米茄
and since these are added together and since we have the linear
并且由于这些加在一起，并且，因为我们有线性
linearity property these are added together
线性度属性这些加在一起
and XOM Omega is and the Fourier transform affect safety
和XOM欧米茄和傅里叶变换影响安全
so what we've used is the differentiation property
所以我们所采用的是差异化属性
and reviews the when the arity property
并检讨时，元数属性
right now weekend solve this equation
现在周末解这个方程
for y Omega the forty a transformer the output
y的欧米茄四十变压器的输出
in terms of Xserve Omega the Fourier transform
在欧米茄的Xserve傅里叶变换的计算
the input and a simple algebraic step
输入和一个简单的代数步骤
gets s to this expression so the for a chance for the output is one over
得到s到这个表达式，因此在用于输出的机会是
Jamaica plus a
牙买加更长
ties the forty a transformer the input and I just simply repeated
绑四十变压器的输入，我只是简单地重复
that equation appear
这个等式出现
now so far this is algebra
目前为止，这是代数
and and question is now how do we interpret this
和和问题是现在我们怎么解释这个
well we know that the for a transformer the output
好，我们知道，对于一个变压器输出
is the forty a transformer the input times the Fourier transform
是40的变压器的输入次数的傅立叶变换
are the impulse response to the system namely the frequency response
是到系统即频率响应的脉冲响应
so in fact if we think love
所以实际上，如果我们觉得爱情
a chip tanh Omega as a Fourier transform pair
一个芯片的tanh欧米茄作为傅立叶变换对
then is the convolution property that lets us
然后就是卷积属性，让我们
quaid this term with
奎德这个词用
H Omega so here
ħ欧米茄所以这里
were using the convolution property
采用卷积属性
and so we know what the 48 transform
所以我们知道48变换什么
or the impulse responses they only one over
或脉冲响应，他们只有一个过
J Omega plus a now
Ĵ欧米茄加上现在
in we may have for example what is in our problem
在我们可能有例如什么是我们的问题
instead of getting the frequency response to get the impulse response
而不是得到的频率响应得到的脉冲响应
and there are a variety of ways that we can't do this we can attempt to go
和有各种不同的方式，我们不能做到这一点，我们可以尝试去
through the inverse Fourier transform expression
通过傅立叶逆变换表达式
but in fact one of the most useful ways is their formally called
但实际上最有用的方式之一是其正式命名为
the inspection method informally
该检查方法非正式
its called if you work that out going one way
它如果你的工作是走出去的一种方法叫
then you ought to remember the answer so that you know how to get back
那么你应该记得答案，让你知道如何找回
method so what that says is
方法等什么，说的是
remember dead we worked an example and in fact I showed you the example
记得死了我们的工作的例子，其实我给你看的例子
earlier in the lecture that
此前在该演讲
the Fourier transform a view to the minus eighty times a step
傅立叶变换以期减去80倍了一步
is one over J Omega plus a
是一个比Ĵ欧米茄加上
so what is the inverse Fourier transform a 1-over J Omega plus a
那么什么是傅立叶逆变换的1比Ĵ欧米茄加上
well ants need to the minus eighty
还有蚂蚁需要在零下80
times unit step
时间单位阶跃
and that's just simply remembering in essence this particular transformed pier
而这只是简单地记住在本质上，这尤其是码头改造
well I've drawn graphically
嗯，我用图形绘制
the magnitude of the Fourier transform here
的傅立叶变换的幅度变换此处
and below it we have the impulse response
和它下面我们有冲激响应
the apostle spines is as I just indicated either -80
使徒刺是我刚才指出无论是-80
times you see now let's go back up and look at
你现在看到的时候，让我们回去了，看看
the magnitude over the frequency response
的幅度在频率响应
and given just a little bit of discussion that we had
并给予讨论，我们有只是一点点
previously about filtering you should be able to
此前关于过滤你应该能够
in for something about the filtering characteristics
在对一些有关的滤波特性
love this simple first-order differential equation
爱这简单的一阶微分方程
in particular if you look at that frequency response
特别是，如果你在该频率响应
the frequency response falls off with frequency and so it tends to do
频率响应与频率降低而下降，所以也容易做
is attenuate high frequencies and
为减轻高频率和
retain low frequencies so in fact
保留低频所以实际上
you could think of the defocus saying that we did on
你能想到的散焦说，我们做的
the imager for EA you could think if that approximately as
热像仪​​对EA，你可以想，如果，大约为
similar to the kind of filtering action that you would get
类似的那种过滤作用，你会得到
by passing a signal through a first-order differential equation
通过一阶差分方程传递一个信号
okay now just illustrate in one
还好现在只是说明在一个
additional step in both evaluating inverse transforms and using Fourier
在这两个评估逆变换，并使用傅立叶额外的步骤
transform properties
转换属性
to solve a near constant coefficient differential equations
解决了附近常系数微分方程
let's take this same example and rather
让我们同样的例子，而
then finding the impulse response let's find the response
然后找到的脉冲响应，让我们找到响应
to another exponential input
另一个输入指数
now we could of course do that using the convolution integral we just got the
现在，我们当然可以做到这一点使用卷积积分，我们刚刚得到的
impulse response so we can put that
脉冲响应，所以我们可以把那
through the convolution integral to get the response to this input
通过卷积积分获得响应该输入
but let's do it instead by going back to the differential equation
但让我们做它，而不是通过返回的微分方程
and so here i'm taking a differential equation
所以在这里我要带一个微分方程
all choose just to have some numbers to work with
所有的选择只是有一些数字与合作
a equal to 2 and now
一个等于2和现在
I'll choose an exponential on the right hand side either minus tee times you
我会选择在右手边的指数减去任开球时间你
have t
呈现T
and again we for EA transform the equation
又一次，我们对EA变换方程
and we can remember
我们能记住
this particular Fourier transform pair it's just the one who worked out
这个特殊的傅里叶变换对，它只是谁制定了一个
previously now with a equal to 1 clearly we're getting a lot of mileage out of
现在，以前用等于1清​​楚我们得到了很多里程的出
that example
这个例子
and now if we wanted determine what the output why if he is
现在如果我们想确定输出为什么如果他是什么
we can't do that by solving for Y Omega
我们不能这样做，通过求解用于Y欧米茄
and then generating the inverse Fourier transform
然后生成的逆傅立叶变换
well what's all this algebraically for y Omega
还有什么是这一切代数y的欧米茄
and and that gets us to this expression
和而那些我们这个表达式
and this is not a Fourier transform that we've worked out before
这不是一个傅立叶变换，我们之前已经制定了
and this is have the second part to the
这是具有所述第二部分的
inspection procedure what we have is a forty a transform which is a product
检查过程我们所拥有的是一个40变换是一种产品
of two turns each of which we can recognize
两圈的每一个都可以识别
and what we can consider doing is expanding that out
我们可以考虑做扩大了这一点
in a partial fraction expansion namely as a summer turns
在部分分式展开即作为夏天转
because the lady arity property associated with the 48 transform
因为与48相关的淑女元数变换属性
the inverse transform is then the song the inverse transform movie to those
逆变换是那么曲逆变换电影的那些
terms
条款
okay so if we expand this out in a partial fraction expansion
好了，如果我们扩大这一点在部分分式展开
and you can just verify that
你可以只验证
if you add these two together you get back to where we started
如果您一起加入这两个你回到我们开始的地方
we now have the sum of two terms
我们现在有两个方面的总和
and if we now recognized by inspection
如果我们现在检验认可
the inverse Fourier transform love this we see that it simply
傅立叶逆变换的爱情由此我们看到，它只是
minus either -2 TV times the unit step
减去任何-2电视机倍单位阶跃
this one is plus either the minus the times a unit step
这个人是不是加了减倍单位阶跃
and so in fact it's the summer these two terms
所以实际上它是在夏季这两个名词
which are the inverse transforms up the
这是逆变换了
individual turns in a partial fraction expansion
在部分分式展开各匝
that then give us the for EA transform
这则给我们对EA变换
all y ft
所有的y英尺
her I'm sorry for her rather the output
她我对不起她，而输出
so this is a gypsy that this is why if the
所以这是一个吉普赛人，这就是为什么如果
which is the summer these two exponentials and this
这是夏天的这两个指数函数，这
is the inverse Fourier transform
是傅立叶逆变换
love y Omega as we calculated it previously
爱Ÿ欧米茄，因为我们计算它以前
okay well hopefully you're beginning to get some sense now
还好还有希望你现在开始得到一些感
love how powerful and also beautiful
爱怎么强大，也很美
the 48 transform is we've seen already that
48变换，我们已经看到，
a glimpse or how it plays a role in
惊鸿一瞥，或它是如何发挥的作用
filtering modulation how its properties helpless with linear constant
滤波调制如何它的属性无奈与线性常
coefficient differential equations et cetera
系数微分方程等
what we will do
我们将做些什么
beginning with the next lecture is develop
下一个演讲开头是发展
a similar set of tools for the discrete-time case and there are
类似的一组工具，用于离散时间情况下和有
some very strong similarities to what we've done a continuous-time also some
一些非常强的相似性，这是我们做的一个连续时间也有些
very important differences
很重要的区别
and then after we have the continuous-time and discrete-time
然后后我们有连续时间和离散时间
Fourier transforms
傅立叶变换
will then see how the concepts
然后将看到如何的概念
involved in the properties involved leads to
参与涉及导致的性能
very important powerful notions love filtering
很重要的概念，强大的过滤爱
modulation sampling and other
调制采样及其他
signal processing ideas thank you
信号处理思路谢谢